Rayna Harris, PhD

□ 512-657-2964 | ☑ raynaharris@palisadestahoe.com | 🏕 www.raynaharris.com | 🛅 raynamharris | 💆 raynamharris

Professional Summary _____

I am interested in the Senior Strategy Analyst position at Alterra Mountain Company. I have worked at Palisades Tahoe at Alpine Meadows for four years in the Parking and Information Mountain Host Departments. I have a PhD in Cell and Molecular Biology and ten years of experience managing projects, analyzing data, and making data-driven decisions. My first-hand knowledge of Alterra mountains and ability to strategize and solve problems make me an excellent candidate for the Senior Strategy Analyst position.

Education

The University of Texas at AustinPh.D. Cell and Molecular Biology2012 - 2017The University of Texas at AustinAustin, TXB.S. BIOCHEMISTRY2002 - 2006

Employment

Palisades Tahoe at Alpine Meadows

Alpine Meadows, CA

Information Mountain Host Lead Oct 2023 - Current

- Provide a friendly and welcoming environment for guests and provide customer service
- Manage a small team of 3-5 employees and assist other departments as needed

Lake Tahoe Community College

South Lake Tahoe, CA

Adjunct Faculty, Biology and Chemistry Departments

Jan 2023 - June 2024

- Develop course syllabi, lesson plans, and assessments
- Mentor students in lecture and laboratory courses

Palisades Tahoe at Alpine Meadows

Alpine Meadows, CA

PARKING SUPERVISOR

Nov 2020 - Jul 2023

- Analyzed parking data and model parking lot use trends
- · Established parking structures and assisted with traffic flow

The University of California, Davis

Davis, CA

POSTDOCTORAL SCHOLAR

May 2018 - Apr 2023

- Managed large-scale, collaborative research projects
- Analyzed biomedical data, tested software, and generated technical reports

Computer Skills

Excel, HTML, LaTeX, Outlook, PowerPoint, Python, R, Square, TouchBistro, UNIX, Word

Languages Spoken _

English, Spanish

Honors and Awards

AAAS COMMUNITY ENGAGEMENT FELLOWSHIP 2019

RSTUDIO::CONF 2019 DIVERSITY SCHOLARSHIP 2019

University Graduate Continuing Fellowship 2016, 17

ACADEMIC ENRICHMENT FUND AWARD 2014, 15, 16

RAYNA HARRIS, PHD · FEBRUARY 2024